<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Government on Pavia Daily</title><link>https://www.paviadaily.org/tags/government/</link><description>Recent content in Government on Pavia Daily</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.paviadaily.org/tags/government/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gobblin Gobbles Prime Ministership</title><link>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-19-gobblin-gobbles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-19-gobblin-gobbles/</guid><description>Big shakeup as UPP takes the highest office in divided post- Pavia First landscape. /T. U. Omasz
In what came as a shock result to some, the UPP received a nearly immediate win in the first round of voting with 14 votes, leading to a 15 vote win in the second round. AMP and Renew were left trailing behind with 5 and 6 votes respectively in the first round and 11 votes for Renew in the second round.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister Resigns</title><link>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-16-prime-minister/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-16-prime-minister/</guid><description>Prime Minister Cissonius announcing his resignation to the public and press earlier today. /C. EEPION
In a surprising turn of events, Cissonius (Pavia First) has today announced his immediate resignation from the post of Prime Minister, a development that has surprised many political pundits and the reasoning is nothing short of curious.
In an event announced to the press, former Prime Minister Cissonius announced that he had dreamt last night about Braemari sheep and their ‘soft wool’ and ‘reassuring presence’.</description></item><item><title>PM Betrayal Plunges Country Into Chaos</title><link>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-15-pm-betrayal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-15-pm-betrayal/</guid><description>Premier Minister Cissonius in his cabinet’s offices. /CHRISTINA ONNIUS (HRM GOVERNMENT)
After the cabinet under Prime Minister Cissonius (Pavia First) launched tax and immigration reforms at the beginning of the week, Cissonius has now cancelled the governing coalition with Renew. Several cabinet members were denied access to the government chambers in the town hall without warning.
At an impromptu press conference yesterday evening, Cissonius gave a speech about the great achievements his Pavia First government had made so far.</description></item><item><title>Sixteen Hospitalised In Latest Street Unrests</title><link>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-14-sixteen-hospitalised/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-14-sixteen-hospitalised/</guid><description>A protester in central Pavia City. Experts fear similar demonstrations in the duchies if public demands are not met. /PATRICK ÀGGF
Sixteen Pavians, of whom five currently in critical condition, were admitted to the Pavian Hospital of the Well-Heeled last night as a result of a violent confrontation among widespread unrest in the city. The incident, reportedly involving a scarecrow in the likeness of the Prime Minister, took place around midnight near the docks.</description></item><item><title>Fanatical Tax and Immigration Reform Passed Tonight</title><link>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-12-extra-fanatical/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paviadaily.org/post/2024-08-12-extra-fanatical/</guid><description>Prime Minister Cissonius announcing the controversial decrees. /CHRISTINA ONNIUS (HRM GOVERNMENT)
In an unexpected announcement, Prime Minister Cissonius has launched two new decrees. They are intended to fill the state coffers and bring more immigrants into the city, but many see this political shift by Pavia First as opportunistic and extremely dangerous.
Major entrepreneurs, philanthropists and members of the opposition reacted with shock. Only a few minutes after the announcement, Renew - a coalition partner in the current cabinet - published a press release.</description></item></channel></rss>